Name: Alirun Khamidov Date of Birth: 06.04.2006

E-mail: alirunkhamidov@gmail.com **LinkedIn:** www.linkedin.com/in/alirun

Phone: +44 7884 705214.

Location: M16 OUH, Old Trafford

Fields: SMM, Management, Tech, Chess, Piano.

Profile

I'm passionate about people, technology, SMM (Social Media Marketing), programming, promoting, sales, creating, controlling. For the last 2 years I have been working in SMM, promoting, sales, Administrating in Educational Center. I have experience in management, as I myself owned a 3D design training school. I have trained about 500 students in my country (Uzbekistan) and plan to re-invest in this field of activity, but already in the direction of Artificial Intelligence. I strive to build my career in the Technologies field.

Employment History

SMM (Social Media Marketing) in car dealership

March 2022 — August 2023

My role - increase sales of a company and engage more audience in Instagram. **Key achievement:** 80% revenue growth from September-October 2022 to December-January 2023

Own 3D design Learning Center

October 2022 — April 2023

I founded my own project to teach programming and 3d design, but we started only with 3d design, as there were good specialists in this industry.

Key achievements:

- Taught more than 500+ students.
- We have reached a potential cooperation with the local giant "IT Park".
- We have achieved recognition in other training centers and in social networks.
- · We have created our own online learning platform, which no competitor in our country had.

Administrator in King's Academy - Learning Center

December 2021 — February 2022

My role was to monitor the educational processes, manage the work schedule of each of the employees, monitor the advertising sphere and timely filming for social media promotions. Also, a weekly report on the activities of the educational institution for the general manager.

Key achievements:

- The addition of many different events, which contributed to an increase in the effectiveness of studies among students of this educational institution.
- An increase in the effectiveness of advertising by 75% than it was before me.
- Increased awareness on the streets and on social networks.
- Increase the efficiency of employees.
- · Increasing the customer base.

Chess Teacher

August 2021 — January 2021

I have more than 7 years of chess experience. About 60+ prizes at chess championships. Many of which are first, second and third places in urban and many others in foreign tournaments.

Key achievements:

- Taught more than 50 students.
- Trained four champions of the city.
- Organized events and tournaments between foreigners and locals.

Education & Courses

Started a bachelor's degree program, Cyber Security, Lancaster University in the UK.

Ended Morison Code course: Web Developing course, Html/Css + Java Script.

Started Udemy course: Programming, Swift (IOS development).

Finished 7 years of Music School: Piano playing, 2rd place in the Azerbaijan competition, 3rd place in the city competition.

8 years of study in the Chess Federation: CMS (Candidate of Masters of Sports), 60+ diplomas from competitions, 1rd place in the city competition.